Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-07 (Box 428, Folder 1)
  - August 1996 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-08 (Box 428, Folder 3)
  - September 1996 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-09 (Box 428, Folder 5)
  - October 1996 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-10 (Box 428, Folder 7)
  - November 1996 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-11 (Box 428, Folder 9)
  - December 1996 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-12 (Box 428, Folder 11)
  - Fall - Winter 1996 Garden Guide magazine (Box 428, Folder 12)
  - Fall - Winter 1996 Garden Guide Slides and transparencies (Box 428, Folder 13)
  - January 1997 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 14)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-01 (Box 428, Folder 15)
  - February 1997 Central magazine (Box 428, Folder 16)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-02 (Box 428, Folder 17)
  - March 1997 Central magazine (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-03 (Box 429, Folder 2)
  - April 1997 Central magazine (Box 429, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-04 (Box 429, Folder 4)
  - May 1997 Central magazine (Box 429, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-05 (Box 429, Folder 6)
  - June 1997 Central magazine (Box 429, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-06 (Box 429, Folder 8)
  - Spring - Summer 1997 Central magazine (Box 429, Folder 9)
  - Spring - Summer 1997 Slides and transparencies (Box 429, Folder 10)
  - July 1997 magazine (Box 429, Folder 11)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-07 (Box 429, Folder 12)
  - August 1997 magazine (Box 429, Folder 13)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-08 (Box 429, Folder 14)
  - Fall - Winter 1997 Garden Guide magazine (Box 429, Folder 15)
  - Fall - Winter 1997 Garden Guide Slides and transparencies (Box 429, Folder 16)
  - September 1997 magazine (Box 430, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-09 (Box 430, Folder 2)
  - October 1997 magazine (Box 430, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-10 (Box 430, Folder 4)
  - November 1997 magazine (Box 430, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-11 (Box 430, Folder 6)
  - December 1997 magazine (Box 430, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1997-12 (Box 430, Folder 8)
  - January 1997 magazine (Box 430, Folder 9)
  - January 1998 magazine (Box 431, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-01 (Box 431, Folder 2)
  - February 1998 magazine (Box 431, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-02 (Box 431, Folder 4)
  - March 1998 magazine (Box 431, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-03 (Box 431, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-03 (Box 431, Folder 7)
  - April 1998 magazine (Box 431, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-04 (Box 431, Folder 9)
  - May 1998 magazine (Box 431, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-05 (Box 432, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-06 (Box 432, Folder 2)
  - July 1998 magazine (Box 432, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-07 (Box 432, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-08 (Box 432, Folder 5)
  - Spring 1998 Garden Guide (Box 432, Folder 6)
  - Summer 1998 magazine (Box 432, Folder 7)
  - Summer 1998 Slides and transparencies (Box 432, Folder 8)
  - Fall - Winter 1998 Slides and transparencies (Box 432, Folder 9)
  - Quick, Light, & Healthy magazine (Box 432, Folder 10)
  - Quick, Light, Healthy, Slides and transprencies, 1997-09 (Box 432, Folder 11)
  - Fall - Winter 1996 Garden Guide magazine (Box 432, Folder 12)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-09 (Box 433, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1998-10 (Box 433, Folder 2)
  - Western Campsites Directory transparencies, 1972 (Box 433, Folder 3)
  - Western Campsites Rev., 1972 (Box 433, Folder 4)
  - Late 1972 magazine (Box 433, Folder 5)
  - Western Campsites 1973 magazine (Box 433, Folder 6)
  - Western Campsites 1973 270-1 (Box 433, Folder 7)
  - Western Campsites 1974 magazine (Box 433, Folder 8)
  - Western Campsites 1974 50-1 to 484-1 (Box 433, Folder 9)
  - Western Campsites 1975 magazine (Box 433)
  - Western Campsites 1975 36-1 to 309-1 (Box 434, Folder 1)
  - Western Campsites 1976 magazine (Box 434, Folder 2)
  - Western Campsites 1976 Cover Slide (Box 434, Folder 3)
  - Western Campsites 1977 magazine (Box 434, Folder 4)
  - Western Campsites Directory 1977 6-1 to 350-2 (Box 434, Folder 5)
  - Western Campsites 1977 Cover (Box 434, Folder 6)
  - Western Campsites 1978 magazine (Box 434, Folder 7)
  - Western Campsites Directory 1978 6-2 to 409-1 (Box 434, Folder 8)
  - Western Campsites Directory 1978 Cover (Box 434, Folder 9)
  - Western Campsites 1979 4-1 to 235-1 (Box 434, Folder 10)
  - Western Campsites 1979 235-2 to 389-1 (Box 434, Folder 11)
  - Western Campsites 1979 magazine (Box 435, Folder 1)
  - Western Campsites 1980 magazine (Box 435, Folder 2)
  - Western Campsites Directory 1980 2-1 to 375-1 (Box 435, Folder 3)
  - Western Travel Adventure 1978 Slides and Transparencies (Box 435, Folder 4)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1978 6-1 to 175-4 (Box 435, Folder 5)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1978 magazine (Box 435, Folder 6)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1979 8-1 to 172-1 (Box 435, Folder 7)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1979 magazine (Box 435, Folder 8)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1979 Slides and transparencies (Box 435, Folder 9)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1980 4-2 to 141-2 (Box 436, Folder 1)
  - Western Travel Adventures 1980 magazine (Box 436, Folder 2)
- Other material
  - Magazine cover reproductions
    Scope and Contents
    Contemporary posters and cards containing reproductions of vintage Sunset Magazine covers.
    - Greeting cards with Sunset covers (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Posters of Sunset magazine covers, 1898-1933 (Map-folder 108)
    - Posters of Sunset magazine covers, 1934-1998 (Map-folder 109)
  - Advertisement proofs etc.
    - Advertisement proofs, 1931-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Advertisement Proofs, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1956-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1973-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Advertisement proofs, 1973-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Sunset advertising promotions (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Willow West material
    - Publisher and award photographs (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Mock up for promotional pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Construction of Willow West South Wing photographs, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Willow West property photographs and negatives (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Interior and construction of Willow West photographs (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Menlo Park Office Planning Study, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Willow West plans, articles, information (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Willow West plans, articles, information (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - STET employee newsletter
    - 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 1960-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Historic California Mission photographs by Henry P. Schmidt
    Set of mounted photographs of Spanish missions in California. Presumably an exhibition either at or sponsored by Sunset.
    - Exhibition text placards (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Carmel), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Carlos de Borromeo-Carmel), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Juan Capistrano), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Fernando), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Santa Clara), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Raphael), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Juan Bautista), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Francisco "Dolores"), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Santa Ines), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Antonio de Padua), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Santa Cruz), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Jose, Sonoma), 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (La Purisima Concepcion, San Buenaventura), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (La Soledad, San Luis Obispo, Unidentified), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Miguel), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Miguel), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Diego), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Diego), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Santa Barbara), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Santa Barbara), 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Luis Rey), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Luis Rey), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Luis Rey), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Gabriel Archangel), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (San Gabriel Archangel), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Pala), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Henry P. Schmidt Historic California Mission photographs (Pala), 1939-1941 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Photographs & scrapbook
    - Sunset staff photographs, 1959 and 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Sunset Magazine scrapbook, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Object 1)
    - Helicopter photographs (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Readership Studies Daniel Starch and Staff Vol. 5 March 1954 - Oct. 1955 (Box 436)
    - Bill Cheney So. Calif. Presentation (Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Bill Cheney So. Calif. Presentation (Box 437, Folder 2)
    - ADI Presentation June 1985 (Box 437, Folder 3)
    - Sunset magazine AAF 1986 (Box 437, Folder 4)
    - The Influence of the Pacific Rim (Jerry Di Vecchio) (1 of 3) (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - The Influence of the Pacific Rim (Jerry Di Vecchio) (2 of 3) (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - The Influence of the Pacific Rim (Jerry Di Vecchio) (3 of 3) (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - Spring 1993 Garden Guide transparencies (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous material (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - "Historical:" magazine information, newspaper clippings (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (newspaper clippings, Fairy Soap ad, pamphlet) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Tree Samples (holiday greetings, Christmas cards and artwork) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Audiovisual media
  - Video
    - Tau Demonstration Tape (Box 11, Object 1)
    - Sunset Marketing Video (Box 11, Object 2)
    - Sunset's The West: Back to the Future and The Great Western Adventure (Box 11, Object 3)
    - Marketing Film "The Closer We Get, The Closer You Get", 1994 (Box 11, Object 4)
    - Marken-Cheney, September 1985 (Box 11, Object 5)
    - Sunset- Face to Face with the Changing West (Box 11, Object 6)
    - Marketing Film "The Great Western Adventure", 1989 (Box 11, Object 7)
    - Sunset Prompts...Readers Act...You Win... (Box 11, Object 8)
    - Sunset's Travel Fair, 4/13/1993 (Box 11, Object 9)
    - Untitled (Box 15, Object 1)
    - "Looking in on Sunset", 1984 (Box 15, Object 2)
    - New Sunset Master (Box 15, Object 3)
    - KPIX Evening Magazine, 1979-07-31 (Box 15, Object 4)
  - Oral history cassettes
    - Sunset retiree interview (#1 Ruth Lane) (cassette missing) (Box 14, Object 1)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#2 Richardson and Callahan), 1978-10-19 (Box 14, Object 2)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#3 Walter Doty and Mel Lane), 1978-10 (Box 14, Object 3)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#4 Ken Cooperrider), 1980-05-06 (Box 14, Object 4)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#5 Ken Cooperrider), 1980-05-15 (Box 14, Object 5)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#6 Norm Gordon), 1980-05-07 (Box 14, Object 6)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#7 Bill Mc Grew), 1980-05-13 (Box 14, Object 7)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#8 Bill Mc Grew and Pfeiffer, 1980-05-19 (Box 14, Object 8)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#9 Walter Doty and Pfeiffer), 1980-05-08 (Box 14, Object 9)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#10 George Pfeiffer concluded), 1980-05-27 (Box 14, Object 10)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#11 Al Le Conte), 1980-06-12 (Box 14, Object 11)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#12 Callahan and Richardson), 1980-06-07 (Box 14, Object 12)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#13 Don Campbell I), 1980-06-09 (Box 14, Object 13)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#14 Don Campbell II), 1980-06-18 (Box 14, Object 14)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#15 Don Campbell III, Pehrson, Lyman), 1980-07-04 (Box 14, Object 15)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#16 Hal Mathis, Pat Lyman), 1980-06-15 (Box 14, Object 16)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#17 How, Willoughby), 1980-07-22 (Box 14, Object 17)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#18 Elsa Knoll), 1980-07-30 (Box 14, Object 18)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#19 Martin Litton), 1980-08-27 (Box 14, Object 19)
    - Sunset retiree interview (#20 Martin Litton), 1980-08-27 (Box 14, Object 20)
    - Proc Mellquist Interview by Bill Marken and Joe Williamson, 1989-02-10 (Box 14, Object 21)